Pleased to eat you.
The Meg is a action, science fiction, horror film directed by Jon Turteltaub.
A deep sea submersible pilot revisits his past fears in the Mariana Trench, and accidentally
unleashes the seventy foot ancestor of the Great White Shark believed to be extinct.
Jonas Taylor, played by Jason Statham.
Suyin, played by Li Bingbing.
Morris, played by Rainn Wilson.
James 'Mac' Mackreides, played by Cliff Curtis.
Jaxx, played by Ruby Rose.
Lori, played by Jessica McNamee.
The Meg is a 2018 science fiction action film directed by Jon Turteltaub from a screenplay by Dean Georgaris, Jon
Hoeber, and Erich Hoeber, loosely based on the 1997 novel Meg: A Novel of Deep Terror by Steve Alten.
The film stars Jason Statham, Li Bingbing, Rainn Wilson,
Ruby Rose, Winston Chao, and Cliff Curtis.
In the plot, a group of scientists encounters a 75-foot-long (23 m) megalodon
while on a rescue mission on the floor of the Pacific Ocean.
Walt Disney Studios originally purchased the film rights to the novel in
the 1990s, but the film spent years in development hell.
The rights eventually landed at Warner Bros.
Pictures, and the film was green-lit in 2013.
Turteltaub and much of the cast joined by September 2014.
Principal photography began in October 2016 and lasted until
January 2017, occurring in New Zealand and China.
The Meg was released in the United States on August 10, 2018.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $529 million
worldwide against a production budget of $130–178 million.
A sequel, Meg 2: The Trench, was released in 2023, with Georgaris and the Hoebers returning as
writers and Statham, Curtis, Sophia Cai and Page Kennedy reprising their roles.
The film explores themes of beach, based on novel or
book, deep sea, underwater, shark.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.